let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "BUBBLE SORT: After i iterations of the outer loop in Bubble sort, the i smallest elements are sorted in the first positions of the array.",
        answer: "B. False",
        options: [
            "A. True",
            "B. False"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "After i iterations of the outer loop in Bubble sort, the i largest elements are sorted in the last positions of the array.",
        answer: "A. True",
        options: [
            "A. True",
            "B. False"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Bubble sort only swaps elements that are directly adjacent to each other.",
        answer: "A. True",
        options: [
            "A. True",
            "B. False"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Bubble sort guarantees a minimal number of swaps.",
        answer: "A. False",
        options: [
            "A. False",
            "B. True"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "SELECTION SORT: After i iterations of the outer loop in Selection sort, the i smallest elements are sorted in the first positions of the array.",
        answer: "B. True",
        options: [
            "A. False",
            "B. True"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "After i iterations of the outer loop in Selection sort, the i largest elements are sorted in the last positions of the array.",
        answer: "B. False",
        options: [
            "A. True",
            "B. False"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Selection sort only swaps elements that are directly adjacent to each other.",
        answer: "B. False",
        options: [
            "A. True",
            "B. False"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Selection sort guarantees a minimal number of swaps",
        answer: "A. True",
        options: [
            "A. True",
            "B. False"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "INSERTION SORT: After i iterations of the outer loop in Insertion sort, the i smallest elements are sorted in the first positions of the array.",
        answer: "A. True",
        options: [
            "A. True",
            "B. False"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "After i iterations of the outer loop in Insertion sort, the i largest elements are sorted in the last positions of the array.",
        answer: "A. False",
        options: [
            "A. False",
            "B. True"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Insertion sort only swaps elements directly adjacent to each other",
        answer: "A. True",
        options: [
            "A. True",
            "B. False"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Insertion sort guarantees a minimal number of swaps",
        answer: "B. False",
        options: [
            "A. True",
            "B. False"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Wich of these sorting algorithms is not in-place",
        answer: "C. Merge sort",
        options: [
            "A. Insertion sort",
            "B. Heap sort",
            "C. Merge sort",
            "D. Quick sort",
            "E. Selection sort",
            "F. Bubble sort"
        ]
    },
]

